{
    "subject": "resource/American_Association_for_Respiratory_Care",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingDate",
    "object": "1947-03-16",
    "human_readable": "American Association for Respiratory Care was founded on March 16, 1947.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9453921318054199,
            "question": "Which association focuses on respiratory care and was established in 1947?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9448086023330688,
            "question": "When was the American Association for Respiratory Care founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920943558216095,
            "question": "Which association celebrated its founding on March 16th, 1947?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192273020744324,
            "question": "What organization was founded on March 16th, 1947?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.888990044593811,
            "question": "What is the founding date of the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.884257435798645,
            "question": "When did the American Association for Respiratory Care begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118880987167358,
            "question": "Name the date when the American Association for Respiratory Care came into existence."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7353993654251099,
            "question": "What organization was established on March 16th?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151349186897278,
            "question": "In what year did the American Association for Respiratory Care begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5522323846817017,
            "question": "March 16th, 1947, marks what significant event?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=American Association for Respiratory Care was founded on March 16, 1947.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7405_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did the American Association for Respiratory Care begin operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7405_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What organization was established on March 16th?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7405_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the date when the American Association for Respiratory Care came into existence.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7405_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7405_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that the American Association for Respiratory Care (AARC) began in 1943 as the Inhalation Technician Association and was officially chartered as a non-profit entity in Illinois in 1947. While it did not use the name \"American Association for Respiratory Care\" until 1986, the founding date of March 16, 1947, is provided in one of the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The American Association for Respiratory Care (AARC) was actually formed in 1947, but the association itself traces its origins back to 1943 when it began as the Inhalation Technician Association.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states the AARC began in 1943 as the Inhalation Technician Association and has evolved since.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The American Association for Respiratory Care (AARC) began in 1943, as the Inhalation Technician Association.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the American Association for Respiratory Care began in 1943 as the Inhalation Technician Association, and was officially founded on March 16, 1947.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}